[{"answer": "The first moment that I think something really was critically wrong was there was an off-duty pilot sitting a few rows behind and the flight attendants asked him to step into the cockpit.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "What was going through your minds?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "I really can't say what happened to him but I can tell you what I observed.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "What do you think had happened to him?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "If you hadn't been, it could have been a very, very situation, couldn't it?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "That's an excellent question.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "I would imagine there was just huge panic, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Well, we were physically on top of this guy for about 20 minutes while the plane was descending.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Yes, and Tony, once the plane landed, what was the next move?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Piers, absolutely.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "I mean was there a moment when you guys were sitting on top of him, Paul, when given his size and his crazed condition, did you fear that he could break free and that, you know, everyone's lives would be in serious danger?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "You know, I have to say I think we're really just very thankful.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "But what were your feelings as you came off?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "One is, have you had any drink coupons from JetBlue to say thank you yet?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "No, not as of yet.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "I mean, have you heard from anybody high up at the airline?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Today the individual mandate was heard.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "What is your sense from the legal perspective of the way things are unfurling here?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "LIVER: You know, first of all, my heart goes out to the Martin family because I have an 18-year-old son.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What is your personal emotional reaction to what they're going through and if I can ask you a difficult question, if this was your son who have been killed in these circumstances, would you not want to at least see an arrest and a legal process to go through that could determine the truth of what happened?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Well, I believe what George has told me happened.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "What do you really believe happened?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Yesterday.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "I mean, does he feel that -- when did you last speak to George?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I haven't spoken with him about that.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Does he feel it would have been easier now for him to have been arrested?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "If that was all that this story was, I agree with you 100 percent.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "But the fact that somebody could shoot a 17-year-old boy who is armed with just a pack of Skittles and not even be arrested, doesn't that say to you there's something wrong fundamentally with that law and it ought to be amended?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "And here's what the evidence is going to show.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "With hindsight, that was clearly a catastrophic error of judgment on his part, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "The cannibals are the Tea Party, are the Club for Growth.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Who are the cannibals?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Piers, I'm not talking about the dogs.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Isn't that the reality?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "These bodies are buried in ended careers.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Well, where are these bodies buried?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I think it is plainly going to be Romney as the nominee.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Is it time for Newt Gingrich or Ron Paul or Rick Santorum to throw the towel in?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Any time you're around greatness, like I was for six years, and you see it at close quarters, you're asked about it.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "What was the purpose in writing it?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "That's a lot of time to spend with a player.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "I mean, as far as coach and player goes, it doesn't get much closer than that, does it?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Well, very complex.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "What did you make of him as a man?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Well, I'm certainly not the first coach that's ever written a book.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "How do you respond to that?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, those rules are not written rules.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What's your response to him?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "No, not in any way, shape or form.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "So I'm going to make money out of his intimate life in the way you have done?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "No, I couldn't because the first, you know, inkling that there might be a problem was Mark Steinberg, Tiger's agent, called me and told me that there was going to be an article coming out in \"The National Enquirer,\" but that it wasn't true.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Could you quite believe what you were hearing when all these stories began to come out?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "I don't think it would be my place necessarily as a coach, but it would be my place, I feel like, as a friend.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Would you have done if you had known?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "You know, I think he's probably softened some.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Do you feel that he's changed at all since the scandal?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "He's definitely striking the ball well.", "docId": "120327pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Could he win the Masters this year, do you think?", "qSentId": 554}]